ccgmining.com 2019-07-28

# Privacy Policy - CCG Mining

As the operator of the CCG Mining website (https://www.ccgmining.com/), our company (Company, we or us) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. The data controller is the Company. We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. Being transparent and providing accessible information to our users about how we use your personal data is a key element of the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA) and the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

### 1\. Information Collection

“Personal Data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable person. We collect information you provide us when creating an account for the Service. We also use different technologies to collect and store information, including cookies, local storage, such as browser web storage and server logs. By using the Service or accepting the terms of our Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 1.1. Account Creation Information

When you sign up for the Service or create an account on the Site, we collect and use the Personal Data you provide to us such as your name, email address, or billing information, credit card information, cryptocurrency wallet address, IP address, or other data that can be reasonably linked to such information by CCG Mining, such as information we associate with your CCG Mining Account and the Service provided to you.

### 1.2. Log Information

CCG Mining collects information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site and log into your account (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

### 1.3. Information on Cookies

We use “cookies” to allow the Site to recognize your browser and store user preferences and other information. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies.

### 2\. Compliance with Laws

We will disclose your Personal Data where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect them as is set forth in the General Data Protection Regulation of the European Union. Residents of the European Union, the European Economic Area and Switzerland who visit the Site or use the Service have the following legal data protection rights under the relevant legal conditions: right to information, right to erasure, right to rectification, right to access by the data subject (Article 15 GDPR), right to deletion (Article 17 GDPR), right to correction (Article 16 GDPR), right to restriction of processing (Article 18 GDPR), right to data portability (Article 20 GDPR), right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority (Article 77 GDPR), right to withdraw consent (Article 7 (3) GDPR) as well as the right to object to particular data processing measures (Article 21 GDPR). These users have the right of access of their Personal Data and may at any time unsubscribe from our newsletter.

### 3\. Security

CCG Mining has designed the technologies that protect your personal information 100% secure. The security of Personal Data is important to us, but we remind users that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. We can only guarantee that we will do our best to keep your data safe.

### 4\. Children’s Privacy

The Site is not directed at person under the age of eighteen (18). In general, and with certain exception, privacy laws, including the General Data Protection Regulation, generally require that the collection of Personal Data of persons under the age of sixteen (16) (“Children”) requires parental consent. Further, if the member state of the European Union has not provided a lower age limit (provided that such lower age is not under 13 years), the General Data Protection Regulation obliges parents to give a consent. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we discover that a person under the age of 16 has provided use us with Personal Data, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.

### 5\. Changes to your Personal Data

In the event we decide to use your Personal Data for any purpose other than as stated in this Privacy Policy Statement, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the usage of your Personal Data for those other purposes. From time to time, we may send emails to you regarding new services, releases and upcoming events. You may select “unsubscribe” , function present in every email we send. However, users of the Service shall continue to receive essential Service related emails.

### 6\. Customer Rights

\- A Customer has the right to access a personal information that is collected or used by CCG Mining.   
\- A Customer can change, update or fix the data.   
\- A Customer can ask us for a copy of a personal data.   
\- A Customer can ask us to delete personal information.

### 7\. Newsletter

Users may subscribe to our Newsletter through the Site to receive information about the Service and new service offerings. To receive our Newsletter, users have to input a valid email address and will receive a confirmation email to verify and authorize use of the email address as a recipient of the Newsletter. We will store the IP address and date and time of each Newsletter subscription to identify when an unauthorized third party’s email subscribed to our Newsletter. We will not collect any other data and will not transfer this information to third parties except when required legally obliged to for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. You may cancel your subscription to the Newsletter at any time.

### 8\. How to Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at contact@ccgmining.com .
